Hello everyone, this is Ria!
Have you ever been to Korea?
Have you been?
Or are you thinking about traveling there someday?
Are you planning to travel?
Today, I’m going to talk about important Korean culture.
I’ll tell you about Korean culture that you absolutely need to know.
I’ll also talk about things you shouldn’t do in Korea.
First, in Korea, there is a culture of respecting elders.
As you probably already know, the Korean language has honorifics.
Honorifics
So, when speaking to older people or strangers, you always use honorific language.
You always use honorifics.
And not just words, you also need to be careful with your actions.
Actions
You have to be careful with your actions too.
Especially when giving or receiving something.
When giving or receiving
If you just hand something over with one hand like this, it can feel a bit rude.
It can feel rude.
Rude
You receive with two hands.
Two hands
Or usually you support it with your other hand when giving or receiving.
Support it when giving.
Pen
“Here’s the pen.”
“Here’s the card.” You support it like this when giving.
Here you go
Like this
But if a supermarket or restaurant is very busy, sometimes people give or receive with one hand.
Sometimes
But most of the time, people support with their hand.
This might feel a little difficult or awkward at first.
I once watched an American TV show.
TV show
“TV show” is a shortened word for drama.
Shortened word
I watched a very famous show called “Young Sheldon.”
Ah, wait a minute... Is this really a TV show?
It is, right?
It’s an American drama, right?
Sometimes I get confused whether a show is an American drama or a British drama.
So what is a British drama, everyone?
British dramas are called “Young dramas.”
British dramas are shortened to “Young dramas.”
British drama, Young drama
Then what about Chinese dramas in Korean?
They’re called “Jung dramas.” Jung drama.
What about Japanese dramas? What do you think?
Try to guess now.
Yes, they’re called “Il dramas.” Il drama.
Anyway, I was really shocked when I watched the show “Young Sheldon.”
Really a culture shock
Culture shock
The main character is a very young kid.
Young kid
That young main character and his friend went somewhere.
I don’t remember exactly where.
But it was a place with a lot of adults.
Lecture
It was a place where a lecture was being held.
But the kid crossed his legs while listening to the lecture.
Crossed his legs.
Watching that made me very uncomfortable.
Very uncomfortable.
“No, please don’t do that.”
I felt really uncomfortable like that.
Even though this drama isn’t set in Korea, it just felt uncomfortable.
I guess I’m Korean to the bone.
Korean to the bone
In Korea, you don’t cross your legs in front of elders.
You never do that.
If I were listening to a lecture and crossed my legs? That just doesn’t make sense...
But in this drama, the kids are kind of geniuses.
Genius
So they have a bit of an arrogant personality.
Arrogant personality
Arrogant
Is that why they crossed their legs?
Or I wonder if this is actually acceptable in other countries.
I’m curious.
How about in your countries?
Is it okay to cross your legs in front of other adults, not your really close family or parents?
Also, I traveled to Japan.
And I noticed a cultural difference.
Cultural difference
Subway
I noticed a cultural difference on the subway.
On the subway, there are seats called “priority seats.”
Priority seats
These seats are for elderly people, grandmothers, grandfathers, or people with disabilities.
Usually there are regular seats and next to them are the priority seats.
They are separate.
But here’s the interesting thing.
In Korea, even if those seats are empty, young people don’t sit there.
Even if there are no elderly people around, those seats are never taken.
They leave them empty.
But in Japan, people just sit there.
They just sit.
They just sit there.
Not only in Japan, but everywhere I traveled, it was the same.
It was the same.
In Singapore, people also just sat in the priority seats.
Everyone sat there without any problem.
I found that really interesting.
It was interesting.
They just sit there, and if a person with a disability comes, they give up the seat then.
They give up the seat then.
Honestly, I thought it would be the same since these are all Asian countries.
But Korea is the strictest.
The strictest.
They are very strict about priority seats.
I haven’t seen any place as strict about priority seats as Korea.
So if you come to Korea and sit in a priority seat...
People might look at you like, “Huh? What’s going on? What’s that?”
Please remember my podcast then.
Also, in Korea, there is almost no tipping culture.
Tipping culture
When you think of tipping culture, the country that comes to mind is the United States.
In countries like the U.S., you give tips at restaurants.
But in Korea, you don’t give tips.
So when you pay, you just pay the exact price.
If you give a tip, the staff might be surprised.
They might be surprised.
They might be shocked.
I really like that Korea doesn’t have a tipping culture.
I really like it.
It’s really convenient.
But once, a famous bakery made a tip box. A tip box!
At that time, the Korean internet went crazy.
It was crazy.
Are you kidding? Tips in Korea? What is this nonsense?
People got really angry.
Because if a famous place starts accepting tips, other places will follow.
They will follow.
They will start following.
So people got very angry, and eventually, the tip box disappeared.
It disappeared.
Anyway, if tourists start giving tips one by one, tip boxes will appear and other places will follow.
So in Korea, you don’t tip at restaurants.
Today, I talked about important cultural things in Korea.
I talked about culture you must follow in Korea.
Actually, it’s okay if you make mistakes in Korea.
It’s okay to make mistakes!
I think the most important thing is to try to understand the culture and have a fun time. Right?
Actually, besides what I talked about today, there are many other important cultural things.
Someday, I’ll come back with a part two.
Did you find any culture interesting while traveling in Korea?
Please be sure to tell me your stories in the comments!
I’ll include those comments in part two. Okay?
See you next time with a more fun podcast! Bye :)